retrogameguide.com 2013-03-03

# Retro Game Guide - Your Source for retro game information.

This privacy policy tells you how we use personal information collected at this site. Please read this privacy policy before using the site or submitting any personal information. By using the site, you are accepting the practices described in this privacy policy. These practices may be changed, but any changes will be posted and changes will only apply to activities and information on a going forward, not retroactive basis. You are encouraged to review the privacy policy whenever you visit the site to make sure that you understand how any personal information you provide will be used.

**Collection of Information**

We collect personally identifiable information, like names and email addresses submitted by our visitors during registration. The information you provide is used to verify your email and create your account. Email addresses may be used to send information ONLY relating to this site, and users will have every opportunity to opt out of these messages.

**Cookie/Tracking Technology**

The Site may use cookie and tracking technology depending on the features offered. Cookie and tracking technology are useful for gathering information such as browser type and operating system, tracking the number of visitors to the site, and understanding how visitors use the site. Cookies can also help customize the site for visitors. Personal information cannot be collected via cookies and other tracking technology, however, if you previously provided personally identifiable information, cookies may be tied to such information. Cookie and tracking information will never be shared with third parties.

**Distribution of Information**

We share no information with other sites,companies, or persons. The information is not provided to any companies for marketing purposes or for any other reasons.

**Commitment to Data Security**

Your personally identifiable information is kept secure. Only authorized employees, agents and contractors (who have agreed to keep information secure and confidential) have access to this information. All emails and newsletters from this site allow you to opt out of further mailings.
